$   

* View All Products
* Vehicle selected 0 Shop Your Vehicle
    
    Close
    
    Shop for your Vehicle
    ---------------------
    
    Personalize your WeatherTech experience by selecting the make, year & model of your vehicle.
    
    Select Make Acura Alfa Romeo Aston Martin Audi Bentley BMW Bugatti Buick Cadillac Chevrolet Chrysler Club Car Cushman Dodge EZGO Ferrari Fiat Ford Freightliner Genesis Geo GM GMC Honda Hummer Hyundai ICON Ineos Infiniti International Isuzu Jaguar Jeep Kenworth Kia Lamborghini Land Rover / Range Rover Lexus Lincoln Lotus Lucid Mack Maserati Maybach Mazda McLaren Mercedes-Benz Mercury MINI Mitsubishi Nissan Oldsmobile Peterbilt Peugeot Plymouth Polaris Polestar Pontiac Porsche® RAM Rivian Rolls Royce SAAB Saturn Scion smart SRT Subaru Suzuki Tesla Toyota Volkswagen Volvo Western Star Yamaha Select Make
    
    Select Year
    
    Select Model
    
    View Products

* You're currently browsing WeatherTech  United States    
    English Click to select your preferred country/language
    * Country: Canada
        
        Select: [Select Englishlanguage for WeatherTech Canada](https://www.weathertech.ca/en?vsp=1) | [Select Françaislanguage for WeatherTech Canada](https://www.weathertech.ca/fr?vsp=1) language for WeatherTech.com.
        
    * Country: Europe
        
        Select: [Select Englishlanguage for WeatherTech Europe](https://www.weathertecheurope.com/en/) language for WeatherTech.com.
        
    * Country: Mexico
        
        Select: [Select Españollanguage for WeatherTech Mexico](https://www.weathertech.mx/) language for WeatherTech.com.
        
    * Country: United Kingdom
        
        Select: [Select Englishlanguage for WeatherTech United Kingdom](https://www.weathertecheurope.com/uk/) language for WeatherTech.com.
        
    * Country: United States
        
        Select: [Select Englishlanguage for WeatherTech United States](https://www.weathertech.com/) language for WeatherTech.com.
        
    * [Country Not Listed?
        
        View Local Dealers Near You](https://www.weathertech.com/service/dealer-locator/)

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

WEATHERTECH WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
----------------------------------

### Last Updated / Effective Date: 10/30/2024

WeatherTech Direct, LLC and any of its affiliates (together "**WeatherTech**" or "**we**", "**us**" or "**our**") value your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("**Policy**") describes how we collect, use, store and share your Personal Information when you visit our websites, including [http://www.weathertech.com](http://www.weathertech.com/) (the "**Site**").

**We may modify this Policy at any time in our discretion. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.**

IF YOU ARE A RESIDENT OF CALIFORNIA, COLORADO, CONNECTICUT, TEXAS, UTAH OR VIRGINIA, PLEASE SEE THE "YOUR STATE PRIVACY RIGHTS" SECTION BELOW FOR ADDITIONAL TERMS THAT APPLY TO YOU.

IF YOU ARE A CANADIAN RESIDENT, PLEASE SEE THE "YOUR CANADIAN PRIVACY RIGHTS" SECTION BELOW FOR ADDITIONAL TERMS THAT APPLY TO YOU.

IF YOU ARE A MEXICAN RESIDENT, PLEASE SEE THE "YOUR MEXICAN PRIVACY RIGHTS" SECTION BELOW FOR ADDITIONAL TERMS THAT APPLY TO YOU.

IF YOU ARE A RESIDENT OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA, SWITZERLAND OR THE UNITED KINGDOM, PLEASE SEE THE "EEA, SWISS & UK PRIVACY RIGHTS" SECTION BELOW FOR ADDITIONAL TERMS THAT APPLY TO YOU.

### I. WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?

For purposes of this Policy, **"Personal Information"** means information that alone or in combination identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Personal Information excludes publicly available information and aggregated or deidentified consumer information.

### II. CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect certain categories of Personal Information. The categories and a description of the types of data collected in each category are as follows:

| **Category of Data** | Types of Data |
| --- | --- |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Indentifiers** | Full name, mailing address, billing address, shipping address, Internet Protocol Address ("IP Address"), email address, account user ID, password, and telephone number. |
| **Customer Records** | Name, address, telephone number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information. (WeatherTech uses a third party payment provider and does not directly collect credit card or debit card numbers.) |
| **Commercial Information** | Records of products or services you purchased, received, or considered, other purchasing history, invoices, and warranty records. |
| **Internet Activity** | Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, the websites you visit before or after you visit the Site, browsing history, search history, mouse movements, and information regarding your interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement. |
| **Geolocation Data** | City, state, zip code, and country (based on IP Address). |

### III. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

We retain Personal Information only as long as we have a legitimate business purpose to do so. These purposes may include retaining Personal Information in order to:

* complete the transaction for which the Personal Information was collected;
* fulfill the terms of a written warranty;
* contact you in the case of a product recall;
* continue our ongoing business relationship with you; and
* satisfy any legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for individual categories of Personal Information we collect, we consider the nature and sensitivity of the Personal Information; the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the Personal Information; the purposes for which we process that Personal Information and whether we can fulfill those purposes through other means; and applicable legal, regulatory, tax, accounting, reporting and other requirements.

### IV. SOURCES OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND THE PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE COLLECT IT

**Information We Collect from You**

We collect certain Personal Information from you directly or automatically using technology for the purposes described below when you use the Site.

| ****Purpose for Collection and Use**** | **Examples** | **Category of Data** |
| --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Business Purposes** | * To facilitate transactions<br>* To create accounts<br>* To inform our business strategies<br>* To engage in product research and development<br>* To monitor and improve our products<br>* To administer surveys<br>* To place, fulfil and deliver your orders<br>* To take and process payments<br>* To keep a record of your purchases and<br>* To process returns. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity |
| **Communication Purposes** | * To respond to your requests or inquiries<br>* To send you newsletters and updates<br>* To provide information about our products<br>* To send you warranty information and product recall information<br>* To notify you of new products and<br>* To comply with privacy rights requests. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity |
| **Website Management Purposes** | * To troubleshoot problems with the Site<br>* To help improve the Site and<br>* To understand how you get to the Site. | * Identifiers<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Marketing & Advertising Purposes** | * To send you promotions<br>* To serve you targeted advertising<br>* To track the success of our marketing campaigns and<br>* To serve targeted advertising to individuals who may have similar interests.<br><br>We use cookies, session replay software, web beacons, pixel tags and other tracking technologies (collectively "Cookies") when you use our Site. To learn more about how we use Cookies and your options to limit the data collected from our Site, please visit our [cookie policy](https://www.weathertech.com/service/cookie-policy/). | * Identifiers<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **For Compliance and Legal Purposes** | * To protect our legal rights and the rights of third parties. | * Identifiers<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Analytics** | * To perform analytics on your use of the Site and<br>* To understand Site demographics and user preferences. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records |

**Information We Collect from Third Party Sources**

We may also collect Personal Information about you from other sources as described below.

| ****Purpose for Collection and Use**** | **Examples** | **Category of Data** | **Third Party Source** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Facilitating Purchases** | When you make a purchase online, we do not receive your credit card, debit card or other financial information. Instead, that information is provided directly to a payment processor to help us facilitate payment. However, we do receive your contact information and purchase information from the payment processor. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records | **Payment Processors** |
| **Website Management** | We may receive Personal Information from our third-party analytics providers. | * Identifiers<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data | **Site-related Service Providers, including analytics providers** |

### V. DISCLOSING PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may disclose your Personal Information as follows:

| ****With Whom We Disclose Personal Information**** | **Purpose for Disclosing** | **Category of Information** |
| --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Service Providers** | **Business Purposes:** including payment processing, customer service, and performing analytics.<br><br>**Website Management:**including hosting, troubleshooting problems, improving the content and functionality of the Site, and performing statistical and other analyses of the Site. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Third-Party Advertising Providers and Social Media Platforms** | **Marketing & Advertising Purposes:** including to provide targeted advertising and other marketing communications.<br><br>**Business Purposes:**including to perform data analysis and statistical analysis for us. | * Identifiers<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Government and Law Enforcement** | **Legal Purposes.** We will cooperate with law enforcement and other governmental agencies, and may disclose Personal Information: (i) if we believe in good faith we are legally required to disclose that Personal Information, (ii) if we are advised to disclose Personal Information by our legal counsel, or (iii) when necessary to identify, contact or bring a legal action against someone who may cause or be causing harm to, or interfering with the legal rights of WeatherTech or any other person or entity. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Professional Advisors** | **Advisory Purposes.** To receive advice from our professional advisors, such as our attorneys, accountants, financial advisors and business advisors, in their capacity as advisors to us. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **New Owners or Successors in Interest** | **Change in ownership/business successors.**We may share your Personal Information in connection with a contemplated or completed strategic business transaction such as a merger, acquisition, sale of all or substantially all of our assets or stock to a subsequent owner or operator, a dissolution, bankruptcy, liquidation or other similar business transaction where Personal Information may be shared, sold or transferred to that third party, including during the due diligence process. | * Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |

### VI. DEIDENTIFIED / AGGREGATED DATA

We may aggregate or deidentify Personal Information we collect through our Site. For example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of users in a particular zip code. Once information or data has been deidentified and/or aggregated to the extent it cannot be used to identify you ("Deidentified Data"). We commit to maintaining Deidentified Data in its deidentified form and will not attempt to reidentify the Deidentified Data, except and solely for the purpose of determining whether our deidentification processes satisfy the requirements of applicable laws.

WeatherTech may use or disclose Deidentified Data for any legal purpose.

### VII. TOOLS WE USE AND YOUR CHOICES

Please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.weathertech.com/service/cookie-policy/) for information about how we use advertising tools and your choices regarding our use of those tools.

### VIII. CHILDREN

The Site is not directed at children under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, use, share or sell Personal Information from children under 16. If a parent or legal guardian learns that their child provided us with Personal Information without his or her consent, please contact us and we will make commercially reasonable attempts to delete such Personal Information.

### IX. DATA SECURITY

We use reasonable physical, technical and organizational measures to help secure Personal Information against unauthorized access or acquisition appropriate to the type of Personal Information processed. While we strive to protect Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of all Personal Information we collect or receive.

### X. THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SOCIAL MEDIA

The Site may link to websites not owned or controlled by WeatherTech. WeatherTech is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or any third-party websites. This Policy does not apply to any third-party websites or to any Personal Information that you may provide to third parties. You should read the privacy policy for each website that you visit.

We use the YouTube application programming interface (API) services to allow you to access YouTube content from our Site. Your use of YouTube is governed by YouTube’s terms of service and privacy policy and not by our Terms of Use or this Policy. We encourage you to read the YouTube terms of service and privacy policy which are available on its website at [https://www.youtube.com/t/terms](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms).

We are active on social media, including Facebook, TikTok, YouTube, X (previously known as Twitter), Instagram, and LinkedIn ("Social Media"). We may post (or re-post) on the Site and our Social Media pages any comments or content that you post on our Social Media pages. Your use of Social Media is governed by the privacy policies and terms of the third parties that own and operate those websites and not by this Policy. We encourage you to review those policies and terms.

### XI. NOTICE OF FINANCIAL INCENTIVE

From time to time, we may offer financial incentives such as special promotions and discounts for customers who sign up to receive our marketing emails or create accounts with us. When you sign up for these special promotions and discounts, we will collect certain Personal Information from you such as Identifiers (your name and email) and Commercial Information (your purchase history). You can opt-in to a financial incentive by following the sign-up instructions provided. You may withdraw from financial incentives at any time by unsubscribing from marketing emails or contacting us using the information provided below.

The financial incentives we offer are reasonably related to the value of your Personal Information. We use good-faith, reasonable efforts to estimate the value of your Personal Information to our business.

### XII. YOUR STATE PRIVACY RIGHTS

**The terms in this section are only applicable to residents of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas, Utah and Virginia.**

Applicable Laws

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act, (together, the "**CCPA**"), the Colorado Privacy Act, the Connecticut Data Privacy Act, the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act, the Utah Consumer Privacy Act, and the Virginia Consumer Data Privacy Act, residents of those states have additional rights with regard to their Personal Information. We have provided a summary of those rights below. In the event of a conflict between this section and the remainder of this Policy, this section shall take precedence for the applicable state residents. Certain capitalized terms not defined in this Policy have the meanings set forth in the relevant statutes listed above.

A state-by-state explanation of your privacy rights is below.

**Exercising Your Privacy Rights**

Rights Request. If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas, Utah, or Virginia, you may exercise your state privacy by:

* Emailing us at: [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com)
* Using this [webform](https://my.datasubject.com/AzyticSNny3DN3fhE/2345).

_When We Will Respond:_ We will try to respond to your request within 45 days. If we require additional time, we will inform you of the reason and extension period. Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your Personal Information to you. We may charge a fee to process or respond to your request if it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.

**Opting Out of Targeted Marketing**

You may opt out of our use of your Personal Information for targeted advertising by:

* Completing our [webform](https://my.datasubject.com/AzyticSNny3DN3fhE/2345).
* Emailing us at:[consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com)

Additionally, you may opt out of the sale or sharing of your Personal Information by broadcasting the Global Privacy Control ("GPC") signal, an opt-out preference signal, using a browser and/or browser extension that supports the GPC signal. To download and use a browser supporting the GPC signal, click [here](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/orgs). If you choose to use the GPC signal, you will need to turn it on for each supported browser or browser extension you use.

State-by-State

To jump to California, click [here](#california):

To jump to Colorado, click [here](#colorado):

To jump to Connecticut, click [here](#connecticut):

To jump to Texas, click [here](#texas):

To jump to Utah, click [here](#utah):

To jump to Virginia, click [here](#virginia):

**California**

**

CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to know what Personal Information we have collected about you, including the categories of Personal Information, the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information, the categories of third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information, and the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you. A request to know can be made up to twice a year. |
| **Right to Delete** | You have the right to request that we delete the Personal Information we have collected about you, subject to certain exceptions. We will take into account the nature of the Personal Information and the purposes of the processing of the Personal Information. |
| **Right to Correct** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Information. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to opt-out of having your Personal Information Sold to or Shared with third parties. |
| **Right to Non-Discrimination** | We will not discriminate against you for exercising any Privacy Right provided under applicable law. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | Only you or a person that you authorized to act on your behalf may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Information. A parent or legal guardian may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of their child.<br><br>If you choose to use an authorized agent, you must: (a) provide the authorized agent with written permission to submit Privacy Rights requests on your behalf; (b) verify your identity directly with us; and (c) directly confirm with us that you granted the authorized agent permission to submit the Privacy Rights request on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent if we do not have proof that you authorized them to act on your behalf. |

**

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Categories of Personal Information Collected** | During the past 12 months, we have collected the following categories of Personal Information: Identifiers, Customer Records, Commercial Information, Internet Activity, and Geolocation Data. |
| **Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose** | During the past 12 months, we have disclosed the following categories of Personal Information for a business purpose:<br><br>* Identifiers<br>* Customer Records<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Categories of Personal Information Sold or Shared** | During the past 12 months, we have not Sold Personal Information to any third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.  <br>  <br>During the past 12 months, we have Shared the following categories of Personal Information with third parties for the purpose of serving targeted advertising:<br><br>* Identifiers<br>* Internet Activity<br>* Commercial Information<br>* Geolocation Data |
| **Sensitive Information** | We do not use or disclose sensitive information, as defined in the CCPA. |
| **California Shine the Light** | Under California's Shine the Light Law (California Civil Code Section 1798.83), you have the right to request the following information regarding our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes: (a) the categories of Personal Information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; (b) the names and addresses of the third parties that received the information; and (c) if the nature of the third party's business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services they marketed. This information may be provided in a standardized form that is not specific to you. You are permitted to obtain this information from us once a year, free of charge. To make such a request, please email us at: [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com) |

**Colorado**

**

COLORADO RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to confirm whether we are processing your Personal Information and to access such Personal Information. |
| **Right to Delete** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have a right to request that we delete the Personal Information we collected from you. If we have obtained Personal Information about you from another source, we will either: (a) retain a record of the Right to Delete request and the minimum data necessary for the purpose of ensuring that your Personal Information remains deleted from our records and will not use such retained data for any other purpose; or (b) offer to opt you out of the processing of such Personal Information for any purpose except for those exempted purposes under applicable law. |
| **Right to Correct** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Information. |
| **Right to Data Portability** | You may request a copy of the Personal Information you previously shared with us. Subject to certain exceptions, we will provide that information to you in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, sale of Personal Information, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | Only you or a person that you authorized to act on your behalf may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Information. A parent or legal guardian may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of their child. If you choose to use an authorized agent, you must: (a) provide the authorized agent with written permission to submit Privacy Rights requests on your behalf; (b) verify your identity directly with us; and (c) directly confirm with us that you granted the authorized agent permission to submit the Privacy Rights request on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent if we do not have proof that you authorized them to act on your behalf. |
| **Right to Appeal** | If we deny your request, you have the right to appeal. To do so, submit a request to us using the contact information in the "Exercising Your Privacy Rights" section within 60 days of your receipt of our denial. We will acknowledge your appeal when we receive it. Within 45 days, we will inform you in writing whether we have reconsidered your request or declined to do so. We will also provide an explanation of our decision. |

**Connecticut**

**

CONNECTICUT RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to confirm whether we are processing your Personal Information and to access such Personal Information. |
| **Right to Delete** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have a right to request that we delete the Personal Information we collected from you. If we have obtained Personal Information about you from another source, we will either: (a) retain a record of the Right to Delete request and the minimum data necessary for the purpose of ensuring that your Personal Information remains deleted from our records and not use such retained data for any other purpose; or (b) offer to opt you out of the processing of such Personal Information for any purpose except for those exempted purposes under applicable law. |
| **Right to Correct** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Information. |
| **Right to Data Portability** | Subject to certain exceptions, you may request a copy of the Personal Information you previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, sale of Personal Information, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | Only you or a person that you authorized to act on your behalf may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Information. A parent or legal guardian may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of their child. If you choose to use an authorized agent, you must: (a) provide the authorized agent with written permission to submit Privacy Rights requests on your behalf; (b) verify your identity directly with us; and (c) directly confirm with us that you granted the authorized agent permission to submit the Privacy Rights request on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent if we do not have proof that you authorized them to act on your behalf. |
| **Right to Appeal** | If we deny your request, you have the right to appeal. To do so, submit a request to us using the contact information in the "Exercising Your Privacy Rights" section within 60 days of your receipt of our denial. We will acknowledge your appeal when we receive it. Within 60 days, we will inform you in writing whether we have reconsidered your request or declined to do so. We will also provide an explanation of our decision. |

**Texas**

**

TEXAS RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to confirm whether we are processing your Personal Information and to access the Personal Information. |
| **Right to Correct** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, taking into account the nature of the Personal Information and the purposes of the processing of your Personal Information. |
| **Right to Delete** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have a right to request that we delete the Personal Information you have provided to us or that we have obtained about you. |
| **Right to Data Portability** | Subject to certain exceptions, you may request a copy of the Personal Data you previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising, the sale of Personal Information, or profiling in furtherance of a decision that produces a legal or similarly significant effect concerning you. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | You or a person that you authorized to act on your behalf may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Data. If you are a parent or legal guardian, you may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of your child. We may not approve your request submitted via an authorized agent if (1) the authorized agent does not communicate the request to us in a clear and unambiguous manner; (2) we are not able to verify, with commercially reasonable effort, that the consumer is a resident of this state; (3) we do not possess the ability to process the request; or (4) we do not process similar or identical requests we receive from consumers for the purpose of complying with similar or identical laws or regulations of another state. |
| **Right to Appeal** | If we deny your request, you have the right to appeal. To do so, submit a request to us using the contact information in the "Exercising Your Privacy Rights" section within 60 days of your receipt of our denial. Once we receive your request, we will acknowledge and start processing your request. Within 45 days of receiving your request, we will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to your request, including a written explanation of the reasons for our decision. If you disagree, you may submit an appeal to the Texas Attorney General’s office [online](https://www.texasattorneygeneral.gov/) or by calling the Consumer Protection Hotline at 1-800-621-0508. |

**Utah**

**

UTAH RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to confirm whether we are processing your Personal Information and to access such Personal Information. |
| **Right to Delete** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have a right to request that we delete the Personal Information we collected from you. |
| **Right to Data Portability** | Subject to certain exceptions, you may request a copy of the Personal Information you previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising or the sale of Personal Information. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | Only you may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Information. A parent or legal guardian may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of their child. A guardian or conservator may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of an individual subject to guardianship, conservatorship, or other protective arrangement under applicable law. |

**Virginia**

**

VIRGINIA RESIDENTS - PRIVACY RIGHTS

**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Right to Know** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to confirm whether we are processing your Personal Information and to access such Personal Information. |
| **Right to Delete** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have a right to request that we delete the Personal Information we collected from you. If we have obtained Personal Information about you from another source, we will either: (a) retain a record of the Right to Delete request and the minimum data necessary for the purpose of ensuring that your Personal Information remains deleted from our records and not use such retained data for any other purpose; or (b) offer to opt you out of the processing of such Personal Information for any purpose except for those exempted purposes under applicable law. |
| **Right to Correct** | Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Information. |
| **Right to Data Portability** | Subject to certain exceptions, you may request a copy of the Personal Information you previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. |
| **Right to Opt-Out** | Subject to certain exceptions, you may direct us to cease processing your Personal Information for targeted advertising, sale of Personal Information, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. |
| **Who May Exercise Your Privacy Rights?** | Only you may make a Privacy Rights request concerning your Personal Information. A parent or legal guardian may make a Privacy Rights request on behalf of their child. |
| **Right to Appeal** | If we deny your request, you have the right to appeal. To do so, submit a request to us using the contact information in the "Exercising Your Privacy Rights" section within 60 days of your receipt of our denial. Once we receive your request, we will acknowledge and start processing your request. Within 60 days of receiving your request, we will inform you in writing whether we have reconsidered your request or declined to do so. We will also provide an explanation of our decision. |

### XIII. YOUR CANADIAN PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a resident of Canada, you have certain rights under Canadian privacy laws including the following:

**Right to Access.** You have the right to confirm that we hold Personal Information about you, receive an explanation about how we use your Personal Information, and obtain access to your Personal Information.

**Right to Rectification.** You have a right to examine and challenge the accuracy and completeness of your Personal Information, and have your Personal Information amended where appropriate.

**Right to Withdraw Your Consent.** You have the right to withdraw your consent to processing your Personal Information at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If your withdrawal of consent implicates the quality of our services to you, we will notify you.

**Right to Complain to a Data Protection Authority.** You also have the right to lodge a complaint regarding the processing of your Personal Information with the applicable data protection authority. Please contact your local data protection authority for more information.

**How to Exercise Your Rights.** To exercise your rights described in this section, you may submit your request to us by contacting us using the contact information listed below.

**DATA TRANSFERS AND CONSENT TO PROCESSING OUTSIDE OF CANADA OR QUEBEC**

We are based in the United States. We may transfer your Personal Information to the United States in connection with the operation of our business. To assist us in meeting our operational and legal obligations, we may also transfer or make your Personal Information accessible to one of our service providers located either in Canada (both inside and outside Quebec) or throughout the world. When we transfer your Personal Information outside of Canada, your Personal Information may be available to government officials in the United States or other countries. These countries have privacy laws that differ from Canadian privacy laws.

**ADDITIONAL TERMS APPLICABLE TO QUEBEC RESIDENTS ONLY**

If you are resident of Quebec, Quebec law provides you with additional rights regarding the use of your Personal Information, subject to identity verification requirements and certain exceptions.

**Right to Restriction of Processing.**You have a right to direct us to cease disseminating your Personal Information or to de-index any hyperlink attached to your name that provides access to the information by a technological means, if the dissemination of the information contravenes the law or a court order.

**Right to Request Deletion.**You have a right to request that we delete Personal Information we collected from you. We will comply with such requests, and direct our service providers to do the same, subject to certain exceptions permitted by applicable law.

**Right to Portability.**You may request copies of the Personal Information you have provided to us. Where possible, we will deliver the copy of your Personal Information to you using a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format. Alternatively, you may request that we send your Personal Information to another business.

**How to Exercise Your Rights.**To exercise your rights described in this section, you may submit your request to us by sending an email to [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com).

**Translations.**This Policy may be provided in several languages. In the event of conflict or inconsistency, the English language version of this Policy controls, unless otherwise required by applicable law. En cas de conflit ou d'incohérence, la version anglaise de cette politique de confidentialité contrôle, sauf si la loi applicable l'exige.

### XIV. YOUR MEXICAN PRIVACY RIGHTS

The terms in this section are only applicable to residents of Mexico. In compliance with the Federal Law on Protection of Personal Data Held by Individuals, we provide the following additional information regarding our privacy practices and your privacy rights.

You have the rights (i) to cancel your Personal Information when you deem it is not required for the purposes established in this Policy or that it is being used for unauthorized purposes, (ii) to oppose the processing of your Personal Information for certain specific purposes, and (iii) to file a complaint with the Federal Public Information Access Institute at [www.ifai.org.mx](https://home.inai.org.mx/).

You may exercise rights (i) and (ii) by emailing us at [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com) and providing your email address and telephone number, and if applicable, specific details of the reasons for which a rectification, opposition or revocation of consent is requested. We will respond to your petition within a reasonable amount of time and inform you of its outcome through the phone number and/or email address you provide.

### XV. EEA, UK & SWISS PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are located in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, or the United Kingdom, you have certain rights with respect to your Personal Information. Following is a summary of those rights and additional information applicable to our collection and use of your Personal Information.

**Our Role When Processing Your Personal Information.** When you provide us with your Personal Information through our Site, we are the data controller. As the data controller, we determine how Personal Information will be utilized, as described in this Policy.

**Lawful Basis for Processing.** Our lawful bases for processing Personal Information include where: (1) data subjects have provided their consent to the processing of their Personal Information for a specific purpose ("**Consent**"); (2) processing is necessary for us to perform a contract with a data subject or to take steps at the request of the data subject before entering into a contract ("**Contract Performance**"); (3) we need to process Personal Information to comply with our legal obligations ("**Legal Obligation**"); and (4) processing is necessary for us to pursue our legitimate interests and our legitimate interests are not outweighed by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of data subjects that require protection of Personal Information ("**Legitimate Interest**").

We process Personal Information based on the following lawful bases:

| **Purpose** | Lawful Basis | Legitimate Interests (Where Applicable) |
| --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Offering, operating, managing, delivering, troubleshooting, and updating the Site<br><br>Preventing fraud<br><br>Providing safe and reliable services through the Site | **Legitimate Interest** | We have legitimate interests to: (1) have a presence on the Internet (our Site); (2) maintain our Site; (3) prevent fraud from occurring on our Site; and (4) ensure that the services available through our Site are safe and reliable. |
| **Transactions:** Facilitating transactions, such as processing orders, delivering products and services, and arranging for product returns<br><br>Maintaining records of purchases | **Contract Performance** |     |
| **Analytics:**<br><br>Understanding how visitors reach our Site<br><br>Performing analytics on how our Site performs<br><br>Performing analytics on how visitors use our Site<br><br>Understanding Site demographics and user preferences<br><br>Maintaining records of purchases | **Consent**<br><br>**Legitimate Interest**<br><br>_Note: The applicable lawful basis for a particular processing activity depends on the nature of the analytics and how applicable Personal Information was collected._ | We have legitimate interests to: (1) understand our customer and Site visitor base; (2) update and improve our Site; and (3) inform our internal policies, processes, and business strategies. |
| **Marketing:**<br><br>Sending marketing and other promotional communications<br><br>Serving targeted advertising | **Consent**<br><br>**Legitimate Interest**<br><br>_Note: The applicable lawful basis for a particular processing activity depends on the nature of the analytics and how applicable Personal Information was collected._ | We have a legitimate interest to market and promote our products and services. |
| **Communications:**<br><br>Communicating with data subjects about changes to this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, and other public-facing policies, disclosures, or terms<br><br>Responding to requests or inquiries<br><br>Sending newsletters and updates<br><br>Providing general information about our products and services, including new products and services<br><br>Providing warranty and recall information | **Consent**<br><br>**Contract Performance**<br><br>**Legal Obligation**<br><br>**Legitimate Interest**<br><br>_Note: The applicable lawful basis for a particular processing activity depends on the nature of the communication and how applicable Personal Information was collected._ | We have legitimate interests to: (1) provide customer service; (2) respond to requests or inquiries; (3) notify individuals about new products and services; and (4) provide information about updated policies. |
| **Legal Compliance**<br><br>Responding to and complying with privacy rights requests<br><br>Complying with our legal obligations under applicable laws<br><br>Complying with legal requests or processes | **Legal Obligation**<br><br>**Legitimate Interest**<br><br>_Legal Obligation Legitimate Interest Note: the applicable lawful basis for a particular processing activity depends on the nature of the legal requirement, including, but not limited to, whether the legal requirement is pursuant to laws applicable in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, or United Kingdom or another country._ | We have legitimate interests to: (1) comply with applicable laws, regulations and government requests; (2) to seek professional advice; and (3) inform our internal policies, processes, and business strategies. |
| **General Business Purposes:**<br><br>Protecting our legal rights and the rights of third parties<br><br>Addressing violations of our Terms of Use<br><br>Communicating with our professional advisors<br><br>Pursuant to a change in control or insolvency | **Legitimate Interest** | We have legitimate interests to: (1) protect our legal rights and interests, and those of third parties; (2) comply with applicable laws, regulations or governmental requests; (3) seek professional advice; (4) manage a change in control situation; and (5) inform our internal policies, processes, and business strategies. |
| **Product and Service Improvement:**<br><br>Supporting, analyzing, developing, improving, and enhancing our products, services, user experience, and operations, including the Site | **Consent**<br><br>  <br><br>**Legitimate Interest**<br><br>  <br><br>_Note: The applicable lawful basis for a particular processing activity depends on the nature of the product improvement activity and how applicable Personal Information was collected._ | We have legitimate interests to: (1) develop, improve, and enhance our products, services, and Site; and (2) inform our policies, processes, and business strategies. |

**Privacy Rights**

* _Right To Withdraw Consent._ In the event you provide your consent for us to process your Personal Information, you may withdraw your consent at any time at no additional cost.
* _Right to Access._ You have the right to request copies of your Personal Information.
* _Right to Rectification._ You have the right to request that we correct Personal Information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete Personal Information you believe is incomplete.
* _Right to Erasure._ In certain circumstances, you have the right to request that we erase your Personal Information.
* _Right to Object to Processing._ In certain circumstances, you have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your Personal Information.
* _Right to Data Portability._ In certain circumstances, you have the right to request that we transfer your Personal Information to another organization or directly to you.

You may exercise your privacy rights by sending an email to [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com). We will respond within one month from our receipt of your request.

**Automated Decision Making.**WeatherTech does not make any automated decisions on your behalf or about you without first obtaining your express, opt-in consent. In the event we secure your consent to do so, you have the right to object to the processing of Personal Information via automated decision making at any time by contacting us using the information below.

**Complaint to Supervisory Authority.**If you believe that WeatherTech is processing your Personal Information in an incorrect or unlawful manner, please contact us at [consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com](mailto:consumerdatarequest@weathertech.com). You also have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority. Further information about how to contact your local data protection authority is available at:

* if you are located in the European Economic Area, [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en)
* if you are located in Switzerland, [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact.html)
* if you are located in the United Kingdom, [https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/contact-us-public/](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/contact-us-public/)

### XVI. CONTACT US

Please contact us as described below with any questions, comments or complaints:

WeatherTech Direct, LLC

+ Customer Service

Contact Us
----------

Visit Our Stores
----------------

* [841 Remington Blvd  
    Bolingbrook, IL 60440](https://goo.gl/maps/5ZEJAUUVe4ZGBVKg7)
* [8741 Destination Way  
    Broomfield, CO 80021](https://goo.gl/maps/4amfbTofM6N1WAhbA)

Find a Dealer
-------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

---------------------------------------------------

Country Toggles the country/languageoptions Change Country

 United States English

Sign up for our Newsletter

 Sign Up

Connect with Us
---------------

* ©2024 MacNeil IP LLC

©2024 MacNeil IP LLC

You are now leaving **WeatherTech.com** and will be directed to 

Close
